Good afternoon ladies and gentleman this is
Sandeep I
hope you and your family are safe,
healthy and coming home
small introduction about myself I am one
with
18 years and I take care of d corporate this is
set is so number
of d series
date we plan to conduct over d next few
days covering diverse topics of your
interest and concerns date you may have weather it is on
your assets n properties marine
cargo liability that date
late d first you know d webinar
fox only on d you know d health and
wellness which over employees
so this event par about and r is ok d
first segment consists of a panel
discussion
[music]
good afternoon everybody
so because of technical creature sandeep
godia is note on video tomorrow right no but
I am taking over and just to
brief date today's wavin r well have
tu sections d first area bill basic
panel discussion a around d covid-19 out
break date this happened  And what what are the
challenge before this and what are the
steps today in the company ICC Lambadi
stocking and in the second area people
doctor Om show is a very renowned
doctor in Harkishan Das hospital to talk about the
current crisis and the questions that you people have
posted offline with this one
they bill post bill post at once we so let me
start by introducing and the panel before this
let me introduce myself my
name is Alok Agarwal I am Executive
Director at ICC Lombard and I look
after the wholesale portfolio of ICC
Lombard and I am very glad to be
present in this first in the series
available
no they have on screen Amitabh Jain Amitabh
Jain is the head of and I think on health
and wellness head of undertaking and flames
and he will be an part of the panel they also have
business Sanjay Dutta and he is the head
of race and on the entire ICC
Lombard which products and head of risk
undertaking claims and  And very scenery day before yesterday in
our stress I am having a problem with
today right from the beginning in ICC
Lombard and
basically further and Sandeep is not there I will be doing the
moderation bill by myself
so let me start
me talking about this panel is
what is the impact that they will have on this
basically effect of COVID 19 on the
economy date I will give me views on and
next few minutes what I thought is the
impact of the economy bill by basically whether people are talking about their
recovery someone are talking about their recovery some people are talking about the
shaped
recovery in my opinion whether some sector which are
definitely getting impacted because of this
someone COVID 19 which they are very well
off but one significant factor that they have to
understand is that India is not
further export intensive country s  In other
countries, you look at China which is a major
export based country and you look at Europe which are it so in
countries in Western
Europe which are very small slice of
Indian territory they are
also very export oriented
sector so what bill are I taking on
this is the countries which have no export
orientation plus two countries which have a huge
domestic population the bill have basically the
bill have little impact so in India in
debt category no this is survey done in
freak and where they have been asked
various people what is the business
impact on cost the various people have talked
about 75% of the people have talked about debt the
bill can be reduction in power
70% of the people have talked about the growth in
sales 61% have set debt expansion plans the
bill can be deferred and 60% have set debt expansion plans the
bill can be  deferred and 34%
impact on exports bill will be there
so
I personally believe it is due
[Music]
Impact of Covid-19 is a concern it will be
shaped to recovery it might so happen if the
government intervention is fast and
quick then the basis of your bill will be and if it is not so maybe the basis
of your
bill will be likely become larger but India will
definitely bounce back because of its
large domestic population large domestic
market its export orientation it is
dependent on various countries on
supply chain there are certain products which have an
supply chain impact but doses are
limited products there are some industries
like farm and FMCG and
computer related IT and IT related
industries which have bills which have a very very
minimal impact going forward so I would not
ask Amitabh Sher his
views
you know are facing
double impact of both an medical crisis today
Well today there is an economic crisis and you
insure that in such a time they style service are
you know customer and are you know who are
members they injured date right from the
month of March some time in the second week and today
also started preparing on a business
continuity plan which injured date you know waiver
morals ready on stall date they are about to
face one de lock doctor was announcer
and what they did is that they
basically put in major initiative in place one was
on preparedness in terms of every
internal process and which was change you can do
so date you can work from home so they
head and business current continuity plan which
go activated and they injured date 85% of an
force was able to work from home they provided wherever they did have
laptop
in record time and provided to this team
and this team in short that you know they started
processing claims through jo r digital and
other  Initiative date they have put place over
an period of time and you know your insured
date what ever clean set per coming you say what
ever service request coming you say
goods bill be handled
insured who are customer were note put then
other kid's problem they provide d a
cashless more you who are hospital networks
further well further d hospital reimbursements pence
you be donation and average they bill you know both
approving the cashless request today well today
d discharge request give you know period
of about 18 minutes
they are also in short that our customer are note put in
you other trouble by enabling what they
can no document letter
seeing date you can scan your document
send it you say they bill play of your claim
and give they bill collect d document letter
they also open and you know in are i bill take
care have which they bill talk about letter
basically and option you and res request
from the up they also can  Attended an
helpline on Covid 19 health way
bill discuss when they discuss up
you sher haj views
hello thank you hello
pleasure with these styles you be able to
communicate through these kinds of tools you
everybody has talked about not only
you know what's happening in the
economy and you know what is in what they are
you taking in terms of
steps on preparing asses and being able to
deliver
an piece of statistics I would like you to
start in terms of me view an global
financial crisis 2018
you insurance operation
investment which 22 travel just having said
date I just wanted you to give you a
small piece of statistics which is
important in the
market par 7.5 billion us dollars you know and
Chinese market howless look at BRICS you
know Brazil India China and look at they
perform you in the next two years and
exactly you know you look at when  Also, just look at the
date of point, the
Indian
2011 has grown by 6.3% correct and you know
initial first air it was 2.5 i.e.
true/6.3 similar with you know you know with
price
no our market is contracting so China has expanded
very fast
and
7.8 vs India 6.3 no viplda so
basic point I would like you to make her because
this is an underrepresented it insurance
market and it is linked to the growth of your
generation what it is always linked to the
growth of and you know by economics
Indian economics and if the Indian
economy you bounce back you know whether it is in terms
of correlation between oil
insurance market I will both her and China
date they would be able to grow and that is a very very
positive sign in put out but it is important to
spot this your
time you know not only look you look and
you know this shows  Help you around which is very very important
per my life
perspective ho do they take your s employees
and everyone in terms of d new normal
items of social distancing which of date but
d more important point is per you be
able to look ahead and be able to if you know
shop assets very d future and per date they have
you know I think lot of d na+ have
already started make you taking place in
ecosystem they are not able to make this
transition you being able to operate tomar
office is which date head go technology and lot
of her in short tech investment not taken after
wever now you use a lot of automation
process maybe you know also auto machine
learning you be able to come to d point where they have able to
start deploying j of it
match on rapid scale which they have to during
this game but d one of d this one of d
most important feature is  Customer they
know what you are able to do but you also can
process data they are
able to
operate every video hero support got
from a risk management perspective
it is important data they are risk very well both
on the basis of you know the
risk switch which are related to this situation and you know along
with Aadhar card is
traffic police and also did the next two
part where they would also be like you it
you make sir debt on this front you do not have
additional shops and you would not like
you know at this point you travel
you know like an flood and think you know during the
time in your trying you revive
yourself thoughts what are insiders are so you
try to divide your financially they bill have
you make sir debt on the other cat topics
race you are covered and you would like to help
you prevent two startups if your close your
fact of well and you know  Thanks
oil prices are going down and its impact
on India is going forward no the revenue
collected by the government is also low because
of
consumption coming down and and in the
current situation the
oil production in India is so small that
India is forcing you to import even today when the
demand for the product has come down
significantly you have almost 15 to
20% off what it used to be going
forward no I want to introduce one I
think you so way before 19 was hard and in between and
half back a way
launched an app called iBill Take Care this is
basically designed for convenience of
yours so everyone think it is done with the
convenience of yours top on your
mobile phone and your iPad or any other handheld
device that you may have and give many
features in iBill Take Care app but one think that it is very heavy
on  What is the
consultation
example date mins hospital
is the second opinion where
date in normal force people art
substance suggest and other things which they are not so
sir whether they shunt non gohad and not this
generally going to date
the family doctor et cetera as they have
basically provided this second
opinion copinion
from renowned doctors both in India and
abroad and this second opinion facility has been in
game
or so an and rightly pointed out by Alok
you know this is an up date they bill created which is
like an one stop solution for
your insurance and wellness needs and you know the
bill was
conceptualized about one and half year
d back and they started working on it
from date time and just date you know this
point in time by kam an such an handy feature
available with who are customer date in any time when
you want to have zero contact they don't want  If
you venture out of your home,
you don't want to take any risk of
going to an OPD clinic and doctor's
services. It can be very handy.
Just to introduce the app, you don't want the
bill to take care of any
features. But you began with it.
Once you have a policy with your group, you can view
policy
related details and your e-cards right on the
app, and then you can check your
policy features. You can request addition
of members, edit other details. You want to do
on your card, track and also donate from the
app itself. You can raise notification
requests as well. You can donate
directly by the company, consult with
your healthcare provider, or do the related policy.
Coming to the network and wellness
services, they have a whole host of features where
they can actually display which
network hospital you are visiting. On the touch of a button, you can
connect with a doctor for
consultation, you can lose your claims both.
Cashless today well today dreams
they have an OPD service where they have peter
doctor area where you can actually
schedule an appointment with doctor you can
available cashless
medicines you can avail of cashless you know an
features on
getting yourself checked at other
you know diagnostic center so last of the
features is but particular as n look mention
they have this feature called hello doctor which is called
consultation feature and by touch of this
icon you know you get and option on you you want to see your appointment
tomorrow
from a doctor and if you say yes with in a
few minutes an MBBS doctor bill get in
touch with you and check on your conditions and which
over d counters dat are der can be
prescribed by this doctor in which case you have an situation
and n condition where is
this diagnosis doctor give only the bill
ask you to you know kid of co on a physical
consultation so this  Assured date you have a
zero contact situation where you can
easily avail a qualified doctor sitting at
your home and if you are not sure about the
services of a doctor
over the phone call and it is very simple
please call who are the policy holder and
part of the policy wherever you purchase the particular call but if you have not during these
times of Covid they are not able to call which are coming
absolutely free you who are D members who have
policies so that something they have taken
an initiative so if you did any
of this feature you get it and you know
sitting at your home and you are able to use this
Telegram feature next I would like to talk about the
Covid 19 area that they simply
created in the up just to insure
date you can get and you know yourself  If you have checked any
other kind of symptoms then it is not
enabled with Covid and record date they have put
date in place by answering any questions
date are you aware of and manage you and if
your particular condition can be
diagnosed further and severe and high risk or
medium risk and loris and basis date you can again take and either
going through
teleconference and physical concentration and as per
the ICMR guidelines get in touch with
any government approved facility also they have put an
information board where directly
connects you to authentic
information about any hospital or
servicing the lab data are available and lot of
other information and they have also created
any blog area where you know when you are at
home you have issues about and
managing your physical fitness about your
stress about and nutrition etc so you
get a lot of articles over  If you have any
queries regarding the COVID-19 related areas, if ...
Features and finally if you look
at the OPD area which I talked about earlier
dates and meet a doctor area where they have
created the three aspects of
doctor consultation pharmacy diagnostic
and health checkup which everything you do with your
consultation requirement with the doctor and the
beauty of this is this which is
available in a cashless system where you are not
required you pay anything you take in this and everything is
absolutely cashless and you know with the
touch of a button so date has features date you
wanted you talk about and this is the time when
you know you can actually try these things about your
problem and
you can actually set up home and a
wheel of this
so thank you with you no I bill request
Sanjay you talk about which and new
products date they have introduced which in a
specific forward and  What are the options that
they have on our customer and Peter
hello
what you clarify
which of an
normality policy is this are in you tax 19 so
they basically men hospital of foreign time
in hospital where ever
recruitment are one 19 treatment
you know it's tax you can be able to
provide you no coverage and that
too 19 further an stand loan
directed with Govinda
looking at device certain customized
products but people would like you give us you know everything
investment basis what density last but not dali that
bin d and of industry
by
you know coming becoming an kid of an tax which is just
bill launch d which bill tax
on d match per
match per broder basis with some or shirt from
1 lakh to five lakh just you know come back to
d specific of its product
view I like you start with d benefit
product so what you device this product on this
situations where if you are
deducted  With co with 19 give you get an
straight out 20 action d deduction is basis
d test which means of conduct by d
testing process
and after 14 days from n really n kare just after
14 days it is your deducted d
you get an play out immediately you would goes
your account you know you have bin you know
jivan this a late d kare of course they are
finally get with water after about
telecast and in b summer family system in
how you leave you n you know co you your
hospital d full idea of ​​this entire
cupboard is you date you are you have got
symptoms need you be quarantined at home you
you are do and take care lot of treatment at
home
so this is one immediate kind of coverage which they are
able to give you an
partner so k with s you be able to give it to
dewar you know kid of customer and maybe
you dear advice you know date is one part
similar kid of  Approach is being you know weight
on it only product on a real
investment basis and
particular product they are billing and lot of
you know over the counter products where such
coverage is available to employees of you know
small company which do not have such caterers ever
covered by yes i see hot bird note the
date which k d stock position country note they know you know an kind of
factorial this kind
of situations so in this side of situation they
have device small lovers which you know it can be given
us your workers which were d what is come back
you k and d government is
mandatory date bill can be bing your k is back you k you
have medical fabric spices
and last but not the list the whole idea was
you have an comprehensive product also which
take care of normally k
19 but you know not sir you get it with
similar sim terms it turns out it is something else
This product would be for
lovers and other customers between one and five
lux and d whole idea is you be able to you no give an
product which is kind of
probably and they have one of d most of the
portable products in d market but this
product you can continue further you are
regular product once ko bhi 19 days you can use it per all
you are welcome
so no it's an 4 O'clock and I believe
doctor Om Shrivastava should have joined me this
time
so abhi wud invite do Om Shreya
Shrivastava hoon is an very scenery doctor
from Harkeshan Das hospital tu sher haj hota I
hope haj on life
no
video
or
you can start
[music]
vat actually na no
way construction is
different
in money wages and date this is an
normal corona virus ok they know about d
coronavirus but this virus they have no only
per d last and last ok so in date they are probably only learning about an every de every
dewar  This is more evidence what's new
in the month of January is different to you what they know today what they know today is what
you are going to be
different from what you will learn another about three times once time
so everyday there is something
new date this date is coming
nature it's a little it's little fly and
telling the same because this virus is going you be coming
in our life in multiple send they are
going through the first wave right no way
probably going you be having a second wave
and baby 4th may date is the one biggest way in the way it is different because
of you
look at other and fraction this date
corona virus has head date being the star
epidemic and the mark and the
current depends different to you of solid
items it is different and way not
love different it's going you be in the vix
of the meat you come so I think it's
important cup your eye open
about what mike  Happen from here in d
future and not b compliant date look d
numbers and other part of d world I am
getting butter and stabilizing and the
infections getting lesser I think Kamlesh
Sensi is going to be the biggest problem
in understanding this virus function
where of the common mistake excel people are doing because of this it is
bating so the you know it's difficult
maybe the social distressing is something
date they need to do they need to cup an
cells in an state of do what next long is
possible which is this something date they are not doing
late they have to be doing a little bit little bit more I know
date is there are
multiple problems with the largest amount
of social distressing date is
important date is one second think is
you need to cup your hands cleanest possible time for
long is possible you need to watch your hands have been very tired
this 200 times today must remember
but every day after tomorrow date you are
getting in touch with this potentially infected surface
and every surface date you are touching is a
potentially covered infected surface and it's an surface were dated
Wireless access whether
its left partner mobile buttons are
potential sources of infection
dat you can use it in all d corporate houses
rai viraj you comment on vip using
price of something called something per at
list three and four our time and dat is dat is
sufficient par you you cup cup doing dat very not
3 4 times a day five times six times
a day so this is d you major
today dat can be used in these and cockroach house
like yours and dat bill dat bill have tu
probability tu biggest mistakes dat
people are making in these today's times which are
positive universe
god can have promised a lot of
promises
in d state of being you no look d porn
s being very very potential good
meditation they don't have n kar aate this time
they should have it in n aage well aage
so match being dem jo over d globe you
find n dat something should be happening very hear only
think is it mins tu be
Validity it means you can be simply provable
and give put up a treatment so they are not this brother they are not this brother but
hopefully they will be very so
thank
you later what can be done
best can be done this
time
you are finding what is this best think date
so I think date vaccine development a
vaccine was my come on your table is style
at list
January of next air if date if date if date
January of next air is fabric going you be
earliest time let it bill be on your
table the Oxford Medical School and
University is starting clinical
trials today and today next of today his they speak so
thoughts good news brother
in law my advice its be useful
specially
duff your bag c date I have d BCG
vaccine date I have some merits of d polio
vaccine that I have some merits of they don't know her
thoughts are being evaluated thoughts in
process and they bill no date is ready you be
him they bill no so hopefully another  about
8:10 pm
bikes
what message do you want to give I think that
you need to relax date this is this is not in
infection date is going away in mansar
one month and of d love date it is relaxed
this is know what you should be in our life par jo d
first of jo over jo over jo over d clock jo over
d sea language I think it is an
important real life it is important you
understand date this is actually a
situation date they have brought their hours and
date they need to be careful date please
mistakes and not repeated you should not
repeat these mistakes they should be able to
practice social distancing and
prevent abuse of d environment
doing so for if they learn a lesson at this
time and date is best outcome of d situation
advice they will probably have this kind of
situation happen  you say I don't want you and
this on SMS technology
and date they need you talk about d some also and
change d way function I don't think those
and things
about this kind of situation it is make it's an
pending you go you learn you understand you can do as an
individual
an organization has an community today n
country and do dat you d best of your team
and dat some good bill come out of this in and
very forcefully thank you per your time and I
bill show jo d best
this way questions
they are note taking questions online
because it bill created some kind of
confusion so thank you per participate in this
thank you sir per your participate in this
very interesting
talk and jo d questions dat you have taken so in
how they have other questions they bill
concert offline audio and d next seminar
dat they hall thank you sir per participate so der r
one and tu  Things that I wanted
you to talk about before we close today that one I
think
you talk about were about mental health
issues so one of the effects I would say of
which this long doctor and people being an
hall up in their homes is that they have bin some
mental health issues with people and what are what are the
bases in which mental health
issues have been talked about so I want you to say
this is our teleconsult feature
bill also help so you contact the
psychiatrist and psychologist and I would ask
Amitabh
slightly more about this facility about
mental health issues
you know going forward way bill also by
enabling the teleconsult feature but you know
super specialization of issues where you know you need
super specialist and also on
mental and psychological kind of situation so right now they have a
panel where
MBBS doctors are available but they are  Also
working on the background you see date you know what
kind of services can also be
provided to our customer so today it is rightly
pointed out by you being at home
continuously and this you know continuous kind
of stress date is building up because of the
uncertainty because of the issues date
happening obviously it is leading to some
amount of mental
concerns date in various houses with various
people and they are fully aware of date
they understand date this is also something which
you be address and they will definitely
working you provide an solution in date
space one more
think that come to my notice in the
last 1520 days this date government
ministry of home affairs has come up with the
circular asking date which workers need to be
assured no sanjay i want you ask you one question
date this circular should be given by
ESIC  No and shotted
and have an comprehensive health tax with other
where giving
so you have the ESIC tax
limitations it is in you take care of you know
workers
mostly you know you get in d lot of on the
when more you know k related
elements 10
dewar is but around dat concept so where where
you bill come in d amount requirement
per d retirement is per sophisticated
treatment you know weather and coming hospital and
private you know and k private
insurance policy is suppose you be d best
policy per dat so yes c b difficult you which would need you have this
asia I would recommend dat they take an
supplementary kind of coverage aa you know one more
think dat I have bin this and they have bin an is
showing very
various circulars to insurance
company I believe one circular dat has bin
issues sanjay is regarding d cashless
claims tha cashless approvals and claims
and need you  be settle in an very short
period of time so what do you like you to
light on date i
think date length date you have
approvals with in you our thoughts d
guideline which is
you types of you know one is customer facing
issues where d guidelines come where
hospital sandal you know kind of request
some basically requires you things what is
cooperation of the hospital side in terms
of d data b of course our on
efficiency being able to give it amitabh
already talk about d way they have seen of
gear you 28 and from an out of d office
kind of an situation and last but not d
list of festival
in terms of identify customer and which date
of course
me like you make fool her in terms of
corporate customer i have to chooses with so you know
giving data of d about d customer
getting d way role you know without other delay is
d most important part advise
it  Bill Gate Delhi because way bill note you
find date customer about d list and it
devar is an whole looping getting other
registered with s but about from dat devar is also an other
element d
pressure tales of d hospital pass so dat they have
money tu u 19 piece wich is they are one
of d bill par dat com tu s and ability to
settle dat is also very very important
dat bill cup d liquid it in d system
flying so way you know today n company have bin u you know you know k is
every
hospital u know trying u you clean
facility with dem tu be able to resistance
devar u know dat they get out fast and last but the
list i think regulated prevention is
around ed also per other retail policy wich
jump note get
review and on an postpaid tu basis and
getting your claim speed and in search it is know before i
close sanjay and amitabh is devar anything dat you would like to say dat i have me
time my list out and  asking you some
change some things date they have done with
an first
like you and by saying date you know they
created this facility this up you know date they
discuss d i bill take care app its
solution per customer who d employees out dear you know can
i bill offer service
feedback so date they can cup making it butter
make it more picture rich and possible
you date this health insurance is something you
know in India has you know developed further n
purity kind of remedy you know when you co tu
hospital only dene you know what you need n kind of
health shot I think d they are thank you
move d that process is dat so
biggest think which is important per other
customer you make sir date he is this you know n DOESN'T use n
hospital you know they do not want
you co tu bill no you would want you co
per normal id kind of plant
hospitalization no in this kind of state I don't
Want you to ask you on very matters so do they do they
take care of these kids of you know
time where they are now you maintain a whole you know
help both on a long term and short
term basis the ability to cup
testings you know weather it's you medical care
access you you know lot of doctors and it is
note and look come
and
preventing other help episode like
you be very very this point of they would as an
company like you andrew it him of
who kids of you know system weather of the
alternative medicines website and the everything
on diet and who of date so whole capital of
experience you make sure date you do not have
an health deficiency you make sure
date you do not come and's what they are trying to
encourage you of that date up further
15 further also non ho sub majors and one of the key
critical factors bill be found in
corporate date they cant do this journey alone
today an insure  It requires a certain
amount of responsibility of
corporate no date it is the new normal
you make sir date employees are seeing through social
distancing seeing baby everyone from home
dads and health initiated you know which is it and
perfectly consciously take it I would be
recommended date when they follow date in the
long term today you come out they also way with more
directive on health being watchful
on health conscious and you know
making sir date take care of the hill just
living it you buying an health where getting
you hospital get thats wahi limited so
thank you sanjay thank you amitabh and before
closing let me tell you if you have like this
vanilla please latest no and if there are any
other suggestions on future baby nurse
they bill will be coming up with the series on your
feedback so I will be in the frequency of
week and 10 days bill come up with the andar
and if you want take you be in on a
particular topic please  Let's say no thanks a
lot and have a good evening thanks
thank you